All right.
"School Idol Club"
Hello, everyone.
I'm currently visiting
the Nijigasaki High School Idol Club.
"Shizuku Osaka" "Kasumi Nakasu"
"Mia Taylor" "Lanzhu Zhong"
Everyone's currently enjoying snack time.
Wait, you're recording a video?
So, Ayumu-san, how do you feel right now?
"Ayumu Uehara"
Um... Honestly, I feel like
I got put on the spot.
I'm Setsuna Yuki!
Can you see me, everyone?
"Setsuna Yuki"
Ciao! I'm Emma!
"Emma Verde"
The cookies that Kanata-chan
made are so buono!
Aw, thanks. I'm said Kanata-chan!
"Kanata Konoe"
Hi, hi! I'm Kasumin!
Praise me, too!
You can compliment me
as much as you'd like, too.
Me, first.
I'm not going to let up.
--Move, please!
--So, what exactly is
the point of this video?
--Move, please!
--So, what exactly is
the point of this video?
--What's your problem?
"Shioriko Mifune"
At this rate, I'm not sure we know
exactly what we should be doing.
Sorry this is so sudden.
I wanted to keep a record
of what it's like here.
"Ai Miyashita" "Rina Tennoji" "Karin Asaka"
You know.
Since everyone other than
the fans at this school
only know you as school idols.
I wanted to show everyone how wonderful
you all are normally, too.
Ah, I see what you're
trying to do now. But...
Yeah. Some things won't get across
with how you're filming.
--Huh?
--Yeah!
You want to show people
how things are with us usually, right?
Then there's one thing
we definitely can't leave out!
Hm... I wonder what that is.
Oh, you mean like the whiteboard?
Or like this balance ball?
You're amazingly dense, Yuu-senpai.
I'm so stunned.
Yuu-san! You're up next, Yu-san!
Huh?! Um, uh...
"Yuu Takasaki"
H-Hello. I'm Yu Takasaki
from the School Idol Club.
I cheer all these girls on and
sometimes write songs for them.
I've still got a lot to learn,
but it's very nice to meet you!
Doing a formal greeting like this
is sort of embarrassing.
Okay, Yuu-san! Tell us your upcoming plans!
Huh? Um...
I'll be the one to make all of you happy!
Wow, that's quite a bold statement.
You mean a bold, problematic statement.
I just mean... that I'm going to
support you all the best I can
as a member of this club, so you can
put on the best performances ever.
I'm glad you're
considering all of us, but...
Just who's your number one, Yuu-senpai?
I'm sure it's Kasumin, right? Right?
It's me of course, isn't it, Baby-chan?
It's me!
Oh, it's me, isn't it?
I'd like to nominate myself, too.
--Uh, um...
--It's me, of course!
I bet it's me!
What about me?
It's not me, Yuu-senpai?
Rina-chan Board, sniffle sniffle.
Oh, come on. We all know it's me.
Yuu-chan?
--It's me, of course!
--I-I-I...
I can't choose just one of you!
"I can't choose"